samash.com 2019-05-06

# Privacy Policy | Sam Ash Direct

* * *

Thanks for visiting our website! We fully respect your right to privacy and the need for you to have control of your personal information. We want to make this site function at a level that best serves your needs. In certain areas of this site, we may ask you may to provide personal information to receive a catalog, make a purchase, enter a contest, or subscribe to a newsletter.

We will use this information to keep you informed of things that are of interest to you and to process your transactions. If you make a purchase online, we will only use your credit card number to process your payment – we will not use it for any other reason and we will keep it secure and encrypted. If you have provided us with demographic information, we will not share it with anyone who is not bound to keep it confidential.

We never sell or rent our e-mail lists or mailing lists to anyone, for any reason, except for other Sam Ash companies and successors and assigns, except that we provide customer information solely for the purpose of marketing and administering Extended Service Plans to the provider of the Extended Service Plans we offer. Occasionally we may collaborate with one of our vendors to provide you with information about a new product, a special sale, a clinic or workshop.

## Policy Details

What follows are the details of how we collect, use, and protect the information we receive in the course of your use of the samash.com website. The following details are covered:

  * Contacting Us with Questions or Concerns
  * Collecting Information
  * How We Use Information
  * Sharing Information
  * California Privacy Rights
  * Protecting Your Information
  * Cookies and Pixel Tags
  * Children's Privacy
  * Policy Changes

Please e-mail us or contact us at  
Samash.com  
Customer Service  
7760 Cheri Court  
Tampa, Florida  
or  

## Collecting Information

When you visit our website and browse our pages, you don't have to give us any personal information. We may gather anonymous data about browsing patterns and use of the website, but unless you tell us who you are, you will remain anonymous.

When you make a purchase, register with the site, enter a contest, or add yourself to our mailing or e-mail lists, you will be giving us personal information. We may combine this information with data from other reputable sources in order to serve you better, such as postal address correction data, but all of this information will remain protected under the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you purchase an Extended Service Plan, we will give the plan provider the minimum information about your purchase that the provider needs to administer the Extended Service Plan. If you purchase an eligible product, but did not purchase the Extended Service Plan, we will give the Extended Service Plan provider the minimum information it needs to inform you of the benefits of the Extended Service Plan.

Our site has links to websites maintained by third parties. When you click on one of these links, any information you provide on the third party website is governed by its policies and procedures and is not subject to our Privacy Policy.

## How We Use Information

We use the information you provide for the following purposes:

  * To validate accounts, sales transactions and addresses, and to prevent fraud.
  * To personalize your shopping experience.
  * To tell you about your purchase, account information, or customer service needs.
  * To tell you about products, services, and events, that may be of interest to you (if you do not wish to receive this information, our e-mails provide you with a method to opt out of the e-mail list, and you can send us a note to take you off our postal mailing list.).
  * To improve our service.
  * To administer contests, promotions, surveys or other website features.
  * To place advertising across the internet and sometimes on this site.

## Sharing Information

We do not sell or rent our e-mail lists or customer lists to unaffiliated third parties for their marketing purposes, and we strive to keep your information private. However, we may transfer information (1) to the preferred service providers we use to perform certain functions such as credit card processing, shipping, data management and analysis, marketing and administration of the Extended Service Plans we offer, contest management and similar functions, (2) if you apply for or use the Sam Ash credit card or other financing provided on our site, to the credit card issuer and financing companies, who may use it as specified in their respective privacy policies, and (3) to other Sam Ash companies, each of whom agree to keep the information confidential. We also collect and provide anonymous information about visits to our website and interactions with our products and services to third party service providers who use it to help us to target advertising and to improve your experience on our website, but we never provide your personal information in this context. We also reserve the right to disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, when required by law, to enforce our website policies, or to protect our or others' rights, property, or safety. If Sam Ash merges with or is purchased by another company, the information we collect may be transferred with the company.

## Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, you can request information regarding disclosure of your personal information by Sam Ash Quikship Corp. to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing puposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to sales@samash.com, or write to us at Samash.com, Legal Department, 278 Duffy Avenue, Hicksville, NY 11801.

## Protecting Your Information

We use a variety of security measures, including sophisticated encryption and authentication tools to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secure networks and is only accessible to a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All credit card information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted and sent to our credit card processors. Regardless of these efforts, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

## Cookies and Pixel Tags

We use a variety of security measures, including sophisticated encryption and authentication tools to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secure networks and is only accessible to a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All credit card information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted and sent to our credit card processors. Regardless of these efforts, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

We also use pixel tags – tiny graphic images – to help us analyze your online behavior. Pixel tags also allow us to send you email in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an email message from us. We may use pixel tags to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with our sites and services. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses.

The anonymous information we collect for placing advertising is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third party service provider, please [click here](https://www.networkadvertising.org/).

## Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.

## Policy Changes

We may change our privacy policy from time to time, and we encourage you to return here on occasion so that you can keep current with changes to our privacy policy. This policy was last modified on June 7, 2017.
